{
    "success": true,
    "title": "Questions",
    "data": [
        {
            "id": 147,
            "quiz_id": 42,
            "question": "Astrocytoma is a type of cancer form in-",
            "option_1": "Brain",
            "option_2": "Spinal cord",
            "option_3": "Occipital lobe",
            "option_4": "Both a & b",
            "answer": "4",
            "created_at": "2024-03-21T09:12:16.000Z",
            "updated_at": null,
            "time_duration": 10
        },
        {
            "id": 148,
            "quiz_id": 42,
            "question": "What is the guideline of second dose reduction if side effect occurs during HER-2N treatment?",
            "option_1": "300 mg once a day",
            "option_2": "400 mg once a day",
            "option_3": "100 mg once a day",
            "option_4": "200 mg once a day",
            "answer": "4",
            "created_at": "2024-03-21T10:06:49.000Z",
            "updated_at": null,
            "time_duration": 10
        },
        {
            "id": 149,
            "quiz_id": 42,
            "question": "What is the median overall survival rate according to Flaura Clinical Trial of Osimertinib?",
            "option_1": "36.6 month",
            "option_2": "38.6 month",
            "option_3": "38.8 month",
            "option_4": "36.8 month",
            "answer": "2",
            "created_at": "2024-03-21T10:09:27.000Z",
            "updated_at": null,
            "time_duration": 10
        },
        {
            "id": 150,
            "quiz_id": 42,
            "question": "In ALK+ mNSCLC, brain metastases occur in.........",
            "option_1": "22-33%",
            "option_2": "up to 70%",
            "option_3": "20-22%",
            "option_4": "None of them",
            "answer": "1",
            "created_at": "2024-03-21T10:13:40.000Z",
            "updated_at": null,
            "time_duration": 10
        },
        {
            "id": 151,
            "quiz_id": 42,
            "question": "Which one is correct for Cazar dose recommendation?",
            "option_1": "With food without food",
            "option_2": "Should be taken 2 hours before or at least 1 hours after eating",
            "option_3": "Can be taken any time",
            "option_4": "Should be taken 1 hour before or at least 2 hours after eating",
            "answer": "4",
            "created_at": "2024-03-21T10:15:45.000Z",
            "updated_at": null,
            "time_duration": 10
        },
        {
            "id": 152,
            "quiz_id": 42,
            "question": "Cazar FCT vs Cazar absorption rate differ from-",
            "option_1": "20%",
            "option_2": "15%",
            "option_3": "18%",
            "option_4": "19%",
            "answer": "4",
            "created_at": "2024-03-21T10:17:38.000Z",
            "updated_at": null,
            "time_duration": 10
        },
        {
            "id": 153,
            "quiz_id": 42,
            "question": "The recommended dose of Crizotinib in patients with severe hepatic impairment is-",
            "option_1": "200 mg taken orally twice daily",
            "option_2": "250 mg taken orally once daily",
            "option_3": "200 mg taken orally once daily",
            "option_4": "None of them",
            "answer": "2",
            "created_at": "2024-03-21T10:20:14.000Z",
            "updated_at": null,
            "time_duration": 10
        },
        {
            "id": 154,
            "quiz_id": 42,
            "question": "Lenvatinib shows prolonged PFS in Asian patients with DTC as-?",
            "option_1": "35.3 month",
            "option_2": "15.3 month",
            "option_3": "25.5 month",
            "option_4": "30.3 month",
            "answer": "1",
            "created_at": "2024-03-21T10:21:48.000Z",
            "updated_at": null,
            "time_duration": 10
        },
        {
            "id": 155,
            "quiz_id": 42,
            "question": "For STS which brand is indicated-",
            "option_1": "reganex",
            "option_2": "Zotrix",
            "option_3": "Cazar",
            "option_4": "Levat",
            "answer": "2",
            "created_at": "2024-03-21T10:22:49.000Z",
            "updated_at": null,
            "time_duration": 10
        },
        {
            "id": 156,
            "quiz_id": 42,
            "question": "Which one is not the side effect of Lenvatinib?",
            "option_1": "Hypertension",
            "option_2": "Cough",
            "option_3": "Decreased appetite",
            "option_4": "Myalgia/Arthralgia",
            "answer": "2",
            "created_at": "2024-03-21T10:24:42.000Z",
            "updated_at": null,
            "time_duration": 10
        }
    ]
}